Office of the Dean, School of Dental Medicine Records UA154
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Executive Faculty minutes, 1955 -- 2001; UA154.003; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1979; UA154.003.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1979 -- 1980; UA154.003.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1978 -- 1980; UA154.003.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1980 -- 1981; UA154.003.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1981; UA154.003.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1981 -- 1982; UA154.003.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], UA154.003.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty, 1959 -- 1967; UA154.003.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty, 1959 -- 1969; UA154.003.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 2], 1969 -- 1971; UA154.003.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 2], 1970; UA154.003.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 2], 1971 -- 1973; UA154.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 2], 1955 -- 1973; UA154.003.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 2], 1973 -- 1974; UA154.003.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 2], 1974; UA154.003.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1974 -- 1976; UA154.003.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1974 -- 1975; UA154.003.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1975; UA154.003.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1975 -- 1976; UA154.003.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 5], 1987 -- 1988; UA154.003.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 5], 1987 -- 1989; UA154.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 5], 1989; UA154.003.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 5], 1990; UA154.003.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [5 of 5], 1987 -- 1990; UA154.003.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 3], 1991; UA154.003.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 3], 1990 -- 1992; UA154.003.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 3], 1991 -- 1992; UA154.003.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1993; UA154.003.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 2], 1993; UA154.003.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; UA154.003.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 2], 1994; UA154.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty, 1994 -- 1995; UA154.003.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Appointments, Promotions, & Tenure Committee [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; UA154.003.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Appointments, Promotions, & Tenure Committee [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; UA154.003.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty Minutes [1 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; UA154.003.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty Minutes [2 of 2], 1997 -- 1998; UA154.003.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty Minutes [1 of 2], 1998 -- 1999; UA154.003.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty Minutes [2 of 2], 1999 -- 2001; UA154.003.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Executive Faculty, 1977 -- 1978; UA154.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty (Front Matter) [1 of 4], 1979 -- 1980; UA154.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1979 -- 1980; UA154.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1979 -- 1980; UA154.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1979 -- 1980; UA154.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 3], 1981 -- 1982; UA154.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 3], 1981 -- 1982; UA154.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 3], 1981 -- 1982; UA154.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1979 -- 1982; UA154.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1975 -- 1983; UA154.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1974 -- 1980; UA154.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1976 -- 1978; UA154.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty Meetings (Prior 1978) [1 of 4], 1977 -- 1981; UA154.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty Meetings (Prior 1978) [2 of 4], 1976 -- 1978; UA154.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty Meetings (Prior 1978) [3 of 4], 1975 -- 1978; UA154.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty Meetings (Prior 1978) [4 of 4], 1970 -- 1978; UA154.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.003.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [1 of 3], 1984 -- 1985; UA154.003.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [2 of 3], 1984 -- 1985; UA154.003.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [3 of 3], 1984 -- 1985; UA154.003.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty (Front Matter) [1 of 3], 1980 -- 1981; UA154.003.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [2 of 3], 1980 -- 1981; UA154.003.013.00025 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [3 of 3], 1980 -- 1981; UA154.003.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [1 of 3], 1982 -- 1983; UA154.003.013.00027 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [2 of 3], 1982 -- 1983; UA154.003.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - Executive Faulty [3 of 3], 1982 -- 1983; UA154.003.013.00029 (Box 13)
- Standing Committee minutes, 1966 -- 2002; UA154.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  - Standing Committees, UA154.004.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Advanced Education Committee, 1976 -- 1977; UA154.004.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Committee Memos and Minutes, 1986 -- 1990; UA154.004.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Research, 1989; UA154.004.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Research, 1981; UA154.004.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Clinics, 1981; UA154.004.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Student Promotions, 1981; UA154.004.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Faculty Appointments, Promotions, Tenure, 1980 -- 1981; UA154.004.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Curriculum, 1977 -- 1981; UA154.004.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Continuing Education, UA154.004.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Advanced Education, 1975 -- 1981; UA154.004.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Admissions, 1977 -- 1981; UA154.004.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committee Minutes - Binder I [1 of 3], 1995 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committee Minutes - Binder I [2 of 3], 1995 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committee Minutes - Binder I [3 of 3], 1996 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committee Minutes - Binder II [1 of 3], 1994 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committee Minutes - Binder II [2 of 3], 1995 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committee Minutes - Binder II [3 of 3], 1995 -- 2000; UA154.004.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committees, 1978 -- 1979; UA154.004.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committees, 1978 -- 1979; UA154.004.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committees, 1978 -- 1979; UA154.004.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committees, 1977 -- 1979; UA154.004.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Standing Committees, 1978 -- 1979; UA154.004.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1994 -- 1995; UA154.004.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Steering Committee, 1995 -- 1996; UA154.004.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1995 -- 1996; UA154.004.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Graduate Instruction Committee, 1972 -- 1976; UA154.004.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Patient Care Quality Assurance committee Minutes 2000-01 [1 of 5], 2001; UA154.004.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Patient Care Quality Assurance committee Minutes 2000-01 [2 of 5], 2000 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Patient Care Quality Assurance committee Minutes 2000-01 [3 of 5], 2001; UA154.004.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Patient Care Quality Assurance committee Minutes 2000-01 [4 of 5], 2000 -- 2001; UA154.004.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Patient Care Quality Assurance committee Minutes 2000-01 [5 of 5], 2001 -- 2002; UA154.004.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - General Faculty Body, UA154.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
    no files; only content is sheet of paper that says, "General Faculty Body"
  - General Faculty Body, 1975 -- 1977; UA154.004.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Dean Shira|Dr. Murnane|Monthly Review|Standing Committee Minutes [1 of 2], 1973 -- 1974; UA154.004.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Dean Shira|Dr. Murnane|Monthly Review|Standing Committee Minutes [2 of 2], 1973 -- 1974; UA154.004.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees I, 1971 -- 1973; UA154.004.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees II [1 of 2], 1971 -- 1973; UA154.004.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees II [2 of 2], 1966 -- 1973; UA154.004.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees I [1 of 2], 1973 -- 1974; UA154.004.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees I [2 of 2], 1973 -- 1974; UA154.004.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees, 1974 -- 1975; UA154.004.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees, 1974 -- 1975; UA154.004.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees [1 of 4], 1975 -- 1976; UA154.004.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees Minutes [2 of 4], 1975 -- 1976; UA154.004.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees Minutes [3 of 4], 1975 -- 1976; UA154.004.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees [4 of 4], 1975 -- 1976; UA154.004.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees [1 of 4], 1978; UA154.004.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees [2 of 4], 1978; UA154.004.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees [3 of 4], 1978; UA154.004.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committees [4 of 4], 1978; UA154.004.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committee Minutes [1 of 3], 1988 -- 1993; UA154.004.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committee Minutes [2 of 3], 1992 -- 1994; UA154.004.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Standing Committee Minutes [3 of 3], 1989 -- 1992; UA154.004.017.00022 (Box 17)
- Office files, 1968 -- 2000; UA154.005; 2.4 Linear Feet
  - Dean's Advancement Files, UA154.005.016.00001 (Box 16)
    Only content is sheet of paper that says, "Dean's Advancement Files"
  - Office of Dental Development [1 of 2], 1993; UA154.005.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Office of Dental Development [2 of 2], 1994; UA154.005.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Delmed, 1981 -- 1982; UA154.005.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Office of Estate and Gift Planning [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1995; UA154.005.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Office of Estate and Gift Planning [2 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; UA154.005.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - University Development, 1994 -- 1995; UA154.005.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - University Development|Curt Swinehart, 1993; UA154.005.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Univeristy Development|Eva D. Heroux [1 of 2], 1995; UA154.005.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Fundraising information, 1995; UA154.005.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - University Development|Eva D. Heroux [2 of 2], 1995; UA154.005.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Guam Endodontic Clinic, 1995; UA154.005.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Erling Johansen, 1994; UA154.005.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Phoenix, San Francisco and Tampa Trips, 1991 -- 1994; UA154.005.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Office of Gift Planning, 1982 -- 1984; UA154.005.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Fund Updates, 1994; UA154.005.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Fundraising correspondence, 1994; UA154.005.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Fund Update summary sheets [1 of 2], 1994; UA154.005.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - William Jacques & Co., 1994; UA154.005.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Goldman Clinic correspondence and files, 1994; UA154.005.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Fund Update summary sheets [2 of 2], 1994; UA154.005.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Giving List Dental Alumni Parents Friends in Connecticut and Manhattan, 1993; UA154.005.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Patient Centered Education Committed to Excellence, 1996 -- 1997; UA154.005.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Student Lists, 1976 -- 1977; UA154.005.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Faculty Appointment Letters and Guidelines, UA154.005.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - Campus Directory, 1990; UA154.005.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - Tufts School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, 1979 -- 1989; UA154.005.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine|Division of Advanced Education General Information, 1984; UA154.005.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - Annual Pres reports from Dept chairman et al, 1975 -- 1976; UA154.005.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Reports for Presidents report, 1976 -- 1977; UA154.005.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Electoral Course - Intro to Instructional Design, 1973; UA154.005.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Individual Annual Reports [1 of 3], 1988 -- 1989; UA154.005.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - Individual Annual Reports [2 of 3], 1989 -- 1990; UA154.005.016.00033 (Box 16)
  - Individual Annual Reports [3 of 3], 1990 -- 1991; UA154.005.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Front Matter) [1 of 16], 1989 -- 1990; UA154.005.018.00022 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Bulletin) [2 of 16], 1984 -- 1985; UA154.005.018.00023 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (By Laws) [3 of 16], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.005.018.00024 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Registration Manual) [4 of 16], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.005.018.00025 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Office of Financial Aid) [5 of 16], 1984; UA154.005.018.00026 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Faculty) [6 of 16], 1977 -- 1985; UA154.005.018.00027 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Committees) [7 of 16], 1980 -- 1984; UA154.005.018.00028 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Students) [8 of 16], 1978 -- 1985; UA154.005.018.00029 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Clinic) [9 of 16], 1983 -- 1985; UA154.005.018.00030 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Students) [10 of 16], 1984 -- 1987; UA154.005.018.00031 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Research) [11 of 16], UA154.005.018.00032 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Recs) [12 of 16], 1984; UA154.005.018.00033 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures [13 of 16], 1984; UA154.005.018.00034 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures (Adv. Educ.) [14 of 16], 1977 -- 1986; UA154.005.018.00035 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures [15 of 16], 1979; UA154.005.018.00036 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Personnel Policies + Procedures [16 of 16], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.005.018.00037 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Faculty Handbook, 2000; UA154.005.018.00038 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Dean's Office, 1975 -- 1980; UA154.005.018.00039 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Faculty Dental Practice, 1968 -- 1984; UA154.005.018.00040 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Continued Ed. Courses, 1985 -- 1986; UA154.005.018.00041 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
- Other committee minutes, 1947 -- 2006; UA154.006; 2.4 Linear Feet
  - Risk Management + Safety Committee Minutes [1 of 4], 2001 -- 2002; UA154.006.018.00001 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Risk Management + Safety Committee Minutes [2 of 4], 2001 -- 2002; UA154.006.018.00002 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Risk Management + Safety Committee Minutes [3 of 4], 2001 -- 2002; UA154.006.018.00003 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Risk Management + Safety Committee Minutes [4 of 4], 2001 -- 2002; UA154.006.018.00004 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Patient Care and Quality Assurance Committee Minutes + Agenda [1 of 4], 2003 -- 2005; UA154.006.018.00005 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Patient Care and Quality Assurance Committee Minutes + Agenda [2 of 4], 2003 -- 2006; UA154.006.018.00006 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Patient Care and Quality Assurance Committee Minutes + Agenda [3 of 4], 2005 -- 2006; UA154.006.018.00007 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Patient Care and Quality Assurance Committee Minutes + Agenda [4 of 4], 2005; UA154.006.018.00008 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Research Committee [1 of 2], 1976; UA154.006.018.00009 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Research Committee [2 of 2], 1976; UA154.006.018.00010 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Dental Research at Tufts [1 of 2], 1959 -- 1963; UA154.006.018.00011 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Dental Research at Tufts [2 of 2], 1947 -- 1958; UA154.006.018.00012 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Old Files of Research Committee Given to DeMaloney in 1979, 1976 -- 1978; UA154.006.018.00013 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Extra Copies of Proposals Submitted to 1978-79 Research Committee [1 of 3], 1978 -- 1979; UA154.006.018.00014 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Extra Copies of Proposals Submitted to 1978-79 Research Committee [2 of 3], 1978 -- 1979; UA154.006.018.00015 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Extra Copies of Proposals Submitted to 1978-79 Research Committee [3 of 3], 1978 -- 1979; UA154.006.018.00016 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Research Committee, 1975 -- 1977; UA154.006.018.00017 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Dental School Research Committee Meeting, 1947 -- 1960; UA154.006.018.00018 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Research Committee, Tufts [1 of 3], 1978 -- 1979; UA154.006.018.00019 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Research Committee, Tufts [2 of 3], 1978 -- 1979; UA154.006.018.00020 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Research Committee, Tufts [3 of 3], 1978 -- 1979; UA154.006.018.00021 (Box UA154 Shared 1)
  - Health Sciences Library Committee [1 of 3], 1984 -- 1985; UA154.006.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Health Sciences Library Committee [2 of 3], 1980 -- 1984; UA154.006.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Health Sciences Library Committee [3 of 3], 1981 -- 1983; UA154.006.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Gradute Studies Committee|Advanced Education Committee|Continuing Education Committee, 1981 -- 1987; UA154.006.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Admissions Committee [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1987; UA154.006.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Admissions Committee [2 of 2], 1980 -- 1982; UA154.006.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Curriculum Committee [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1987; UA154.006.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Curriculum Committee [2 of 2], 1981 -- 1987; UA154.006.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Professional Standards Comm.|Clinics Comm.|Instrument Comm. [1 of 2], 1982 -- 1986; UA154.006.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Professional Standards Comm.|Clinics Comm.|Instrument Comm. [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1985; UA154.006.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Research Committee [1 of 2], 1982 -- 1985; UA154.006.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Research Committee [2 of 2], 1981 -- 1982; UA154.006.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - General Faculty [1 of 3], 1980 -- 1989; UA154.006.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - General Faculty [2 of 3], 1973 -- 1979; UA154.006.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - General Faculty [3 of 3], 1959 -- 1973; UA154.006.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Considering Ethics, 2006; UA154.006.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Tufts University Crisis Management Plan [1 of 2], 2005; UA154.006.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Tufts University Crisis Management Plan [2 of 2], 2003; UA154.006.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Grant Application [1 of 3], 1965; UA154.006.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Grant Application [2 of 3], 1965; UA154.006.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Grant Application [3 of 3], 1965; UA154.006.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Strategic Planning - Archival Copy [1 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA154.006.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Strategic Planning - Archival Copy [2 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA154.006.019.00023 (Box 19)